Contato

vgr92@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vitorreisler (LinkedIn)

Principais competências
API REST
SASS
JavaScript

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Português (Native or Bilingual)
Hebraico (Full Professional)

Vitor Gorodski Reisler

Looking for my first challange as FullStack Developer Ramat Gan, Distrito de Tel Aviv, Israel

Resumo

Hello, I'm Vitor, a passionate web developer with a focus on creating immersive digital experiences. I have a solid foundation in HTML5 and CSS3, which allows me to craft visually appealing and responsive websites. Currently, I'm diving deep into the world of JavaScript and TypeScript, as I strive to become a proficient Fullstack Developer in the near future. I'm excited about the endless possibilities that lie ahead and am committed to continuous learning to achieve my goal of becoming a well-rounded and skilled programmer.

Experiência

Wolt Shift manager novembro de 2022 - junho de 2023 (8 meses)

Tel Aviv-Yafo, Tel Aviv District, Israel

AVO

Warehouse Team Member fevereiro de 2021 - abril de 2022 (1 ano 3 meses)

Tel Aviv, Israel

Takeaway.com delivery outubro de 2020 - fevereiro de 2021 (5 meses)

aroma israel

טבח

julho de 2020 - outubro de 2020 (4 meses)

vibe ramat gan מאמן כושר novembro de 2019 - janeiro de 2020 (3 meses) eTeacher Group Account Manager agosto de 2018 - outubro de 2019 (1 ano 3 meses)

Ramat Gan Area, Israel

LaBriut shake and juices Manager 2017 - 2018 (1 ano) Ramat Gan Area, Israel

Co-Manager in a foodtruck

Prefeitura de São Paulo Estagário 2014 - 2014 (menos de um ano) São Paulo e Região, Brasil

Inspect municipal markets, training and awareness of small owners

Savana alimentos Comercial Ltda. Internship Trainee 2013 - 2014 (1 ano) São Paulo e Região, Brasil

Supervise HACCP, SSOP and GMP

Formação acadêmica

wingate

2019 - 2019) · מדריך כושר ובריאות)

Faculdades Metropolitanas Unidas

Bacharelado, Medicina Veterinária · (2010 - 2014)